{"metadata":{"generator":"Captivate","generatorVersion":"10.0.1","schemaVersion":"","author":"author","title":"","description":"project description","email":"author@company.com","website":"www.company.com","tags":"","thumbnail":"","source":"assets","durationInFrames":1410,"frameRate":30,"totalSlides":10,"width":640,"height":480,"responsive":false,"scalable":false,"launchFile":"index.html"},"contentStructure":[{"id":"Text_Caption_331","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_331","title":"Information Security Summer Social Media Quiz ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_574","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_574","title":"Take our Security Quiz   to test your knowledge.    Click on Begin to start. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_575","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_575","title":"Brought to you by the Information Security Branch  Office of the Chief Information Officer ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_9","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_9","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si21887","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si21901","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Slide21706","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_331","Text_Caption_574","Text_Caption_575","Button_9","si21887","si21901"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide21706"}}},{"id":"Image_189","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_189","roles":{}},{"id":"si12441","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_338","roles":{}},{"id":"si12349","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_327","title":"1. Let’s say your friend contacts you on social media, telling you they have fallen on hard times and asking you for some money. You want to help, but feel uncertain, what should you do? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12360","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_328","title":"a) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12364","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_329","title":"Send the money ASAP ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12360_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"175","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Send the money ASAP\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si12382","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_332","title":"b) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12386","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_333","title":"Contact your friend through phone or in-person ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12382_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"179","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Contact your friend through phone or in-person\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si24884","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"c) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24888","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Don’t worry about it ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24884_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Don’t worry about it\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si12435","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_337","roles":{}},{"id":"si12459","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_42","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12473","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_43","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19347","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19361","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19593","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19606","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19621","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19634","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19649","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19662","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19677","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19690","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12405","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_334","title":"Correct - Answer: B  You don’t know who is operating a social media account. Many accounts can be hacked so that it appears that your friend is only saying something strange or a fake account could be created that mirrors your friend’s account.  Make sure to check in with your friend outside of social media to verify what their account is asking or saying is truly from them.    Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12417","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_335","title":"Incorrect  - Answer: B  You don’t know who is operating a social media account. Many accounts can be hacked so that it appears that your friend is only saying something strange or a fake account could be created that mirrors your friend’s account.  Make sure to check in with your friend outside of social media to verify what their account is asking or saying is truly from them.   Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12429","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_336","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide12483","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_189","si12349","si12364","si12386","si24888","si12459","si12473","si19347","si19361","si19593","si19606","si19621","si19634","si19649","si19662","si19677","si19690","si12429"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide12483"},"question":{"interactionId":"12329","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"1. Let’s say your friend contacts you on social media, telling you they have fallen on hard times and asking you for some money. You want to help, but feel uncertain, what should you do?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["b"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_190","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_190","roles":{}},{"id":"si22070","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_714","roles":{}},{"id":"si21978","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_698","title":"2. What can you do to prevent criminals from using a social network site to target you?  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21989","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_704","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21993","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_705","title":"Hire a cyber security company to protect you ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21989_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"175_394","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Hire a cyber security company to protect you\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si22000","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_706","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22004","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_707","title":"Ask them nicely to stop ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22000_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"179_395","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Ask them nicely to stop\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si24737","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24741","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Choose a site that allows you to control who can see your page ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24737_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Choose a site that allows you to control who can see your page\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si22064","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_713","roles":{}},{"id":"si22092","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_103","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide22259q1","for":"Slide22259q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22110","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_104","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide22259q1","for":"Slide22259q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22132","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_105","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide22259q1","for":"Slide22259q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22150","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_106","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide22259q1","for":"Slide22259q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22162","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide22259q1","for":"Slide22259q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22174","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide22259q1","for":"Slide22259q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22186","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide22259q1","for":"Slide22259q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22198","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide22259q1","for":"Slide22259q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22210","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide22259q1","for":"Slide22259q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22222","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide22259q1","for":"Slide22259q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22234","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide22259q1","for":"Slide22259q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22246","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide22259q1","for":"Slide22259q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22034","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_710","title":"Correct - Answer: C  One of the best ways to prevent criminals from targeting you on a social networking site is to choose a company that offers strong privacy and security features. Being able to hide what non-friends can see on your account will greatly reduce the probability of attacks, especially sophisticated ones. As well you should periodically review your friends list to ensure that they are still wanting each person to have access to your online presence.   Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22046","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_711","title":"Incorrect - Answer: C  One of the best ways to prevent criminals from targeting you on a social networking site is to choose a company that offers strong privacy and security features. Being able to hide what non-friends can see on your account will greatly reduce the probability of attacks, especially sophisticated ones. As well you should periodically review your friends list to ensure that they are still wanting each person to have access to your online presence.   Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22058","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_712","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide22259","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_190","si21978","si21993","si22004","si24741","si22092","si22110","si22132","si22150","si22162","si22174","si22186","si22198","si22210","si22222","si22234","si22246","si22058"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide22259"},"question":{"interactionId":"21958","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"2. What can you do to prevent criminals from using a social network site to target you? \r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["C"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_191","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_191","roles":{}},{"id":"si22393","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_725","roles":{}},{"id":"si22301","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_699","title":"3. When you post information and photos to a well-known social media site, who owns the information and photos? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22312","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_715","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22316","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_716","title":"You own them, as it is your stuff ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22312_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"175_397","roles":{"answer":{"title":"You own them, as it is your stuff\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si22323","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_717","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22327","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_718","title":"The social media company owns it all ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22323_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"179_398","roles":{"answer":{"title":"The social media company owns it all\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si24957","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24961","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You and the social media company both own it ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24957_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"You and the social media company both own it\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si24972","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24976","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Nobody “owns” it because it is on the Internet ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24972_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Nobody “owns” it because it is on the Internet\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si22387","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_724","roles":{}},{"id":"si22415","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_107","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide22582q2","for":"Slide22582q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22433","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_108","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide22582q2","for":"Slide22582q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22455","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_109","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide22582q2","for":"Slide22582q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22473","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_110","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide22582q2","for":"Slide22582q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22485","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide22582q2","for":"Slide22582q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22497","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide22582q2","for":"Slide22582q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22509","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide22582q2","for":"Slide22582q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22521","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide22582q2","for":"Slide22582q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22533","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide22582q2","for":"Slide22582q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22545","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide22582q2","for":"Slide22582q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22557","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide22582q2","for":"Slide22582q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22569","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide22582q2","for":"Slide22582q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22357","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_721","title":"Correct - Answer: B  The company that owns the social media site owns whatever you post on their site. It is by using the information and photos of site users that the companies make money. They sell it to advertisers and others to pay for running the “free” site. Read the Terms of Use before posting any personal information and photos. Remember that once it is on the Internet, you cannot guarantee that it can be controlled or deleted and may be copied multiple times.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22369","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_722","title":"Incorrect  - Answer: B  The company that owns the social media site owns whatever you post on their site. It is by using the information and photos of site users that the companies make money. They sell it to advertisers and others to pay for running the “free” site. Read the Terms of Use before posting any personal information and photos. Remember that once it is on the Internet, you cannot guarantee that it can be controlled or deleted and may be copied multiple times.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22381","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_723","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide22582","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_191","si22301","si22316","si22327","si24961","si24976","si22415","si22433","si22455","si22473","si22485","si22497","si22509","si22521","si22533","si22545","si22557","si22569","si22381"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide22582"},"question":{"interactionId":"22281","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"3. When you post information and photos to a well-known social media site, who owns the information and photos?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_192","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_192","roles":{}},{"id":"si22716","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_736","roles":{}},{"id":"si22624","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_700","title":"4. You just got an email, that seems to come from a social media site you’re registered with. The email states that you won a new computer and all you must do is fill out the information card and they will send it to you! What should you do?  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22635","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_726","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22639","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_727","title":"Fill out the card and send it in ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22635_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Fill out the card and send it in\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si22646","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_728","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22650","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_729","title":"Check to see if you want that kind of computer ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22646_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Check to see if you want that kind of computer\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si22657","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_730","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22661","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_731","title":"Throw out your current computer ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22657_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Throw out your current computer\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si22928","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22932","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Verify with the social media company that this is true ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22928_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Verify with the social media company that this is true\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si22710","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_735","roles":{}},{"id":"si22738","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_111","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide22905q3","for":"Slide22905q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22756","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_112","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide22905q3","for":"Slide22905q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22778","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_113","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide22905q3","for":"Slide22905q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22796","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_114","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide22905q3","for":"Slide22905q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22808","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide22905q3","for":"Slide22905q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22820","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide22905q3","for":"Slide22905q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22832","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide22905q3","for":"Slide22905q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22844","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide22905q3","for":"Slide22905q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22856","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide22905q3","for":"Slide22905q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22868","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide22905q3","for":"Slide22905q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22880","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide22905q3","for":"Slide22905q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22892","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide22905q3","for":"Slide22905q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22680","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_732","title":"Correct -  Answer: D  Phishing emails are more prevalent then ever before. Many people belong to the same social media platforms and criminals only need to send fraudulent emails to mass distribution lists in hopes that someone replies or clicks on a link. If you receive an email that seems ‘too good to be true’ or the email is asking for you to give your confidential information, you should always exercise caution and contact the company directly.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22692","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_733","title":"Incorrect  -  Answer: D  Phishing emails are more prevalent then ever before. Many people belong to the same social media platforms and criminals only need to send fraudulent emails to mass distribution lists in hopes that someone replies or clicks on a link. If you receive an email that seems ‘too good to be true’ or the email is asking for you to give your confidential information, you should always exercise caution and contact the company directly.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22704","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_734","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide22905","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_192","si22624","si22639","si22650","si22661","si22932","si22738","si22756","si22778","si22796","si22808","si22820","si22832","si22844","si22856","si22868","si22880","si22892","si22704"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide22905"},"question":{"interactionId":"22604","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"4. You just got an email, that seems to come from a social media site you’re registered with. The email states that you won a new computer and all you must do is fill out the information card and they will send it to you! What should you do? \r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["D"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_193","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_193","roles":{}},{"id":"si23144","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_749","roles":{}},{"id":"si23041","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_701","title":"5.  You are working on a project for work with a colleague who you have on social media. You are finding social media much faster for communication and collaboration. Is it okay to do work through social media platforms instead of the usual channels? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23052","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_737","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23056","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_738","title":"Your employer would likely object ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23052_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Your employer would likely object\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si23063","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_739","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23067","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_740","title":"You risk exposing business information ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23063_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"You risk exposing business information\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si23074","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_741","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23078","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_742","title":"Intercepted work information could be used for a targeted phishing email ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23074_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Intercepted work information could be used for a targeted phishing email\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si23085","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_743","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23089","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_744","title":"All of the above ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23085_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"All of the above\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si23138","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_748","roles":{}},{"id":"si23166","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_115","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide23333q4","for":"Slide23333q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23184","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_116","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide23333q4","for":"Slide23333q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23206","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_117","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide23333q4","for":"Slide23333q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23224","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_118","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide23333q4","for":"Slide23333q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23236","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide23333q4","for":"Slide23333q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23248","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide23333q4","for":"Slide23333q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23260","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide23333q4","for":"Slide23333q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23272","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide23333q4","for":"Slide23333q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23284","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide23333q4","for":"Slide23333q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23296","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide23333q4","for":"Slide23333q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23308","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide23333q4","for":"Slide23333q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23320","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide23333q4","for":"Slide23333q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23108","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_745","title":"Correct - Answer: D  While it might be tempting to keep in touch with contacts via social media, criminals have used business information gleaned from a person’s social media site to harm or exploit the user in the offline world. They have also used personal information to exploit people in their jobs, including targeted spear phishing attacks. Keep your personal and business information separate.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23120","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_746","title":"Incorrect  - Answer: D  While it might be tempting to keep in touch with contacts via social media, criminals have used business information gleaned from a person’s social media site to harm or exploit the user in the offline world. They have also used personal information to exploit people in their jobs, including targeted spear phishing attacks. Keep your personal and business information separate.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23132","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_747","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide23333","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_193","si23041","si23056","si23067","si23078","si23089","si23166","si23184","si23206","si23224","si23236","si23248","si23260","si23272","si23284","si23296","si23308","si23320","si23132"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide23333"},"question":{"interactionId":"23021","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"5.  You are working on a project for work with a colleague who you have on social media. You are finding social media much faster for communication and collaboration. Is it okay to do work through social media platforms instead of the usual channels?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["D"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_194","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_194","roles":{}},{"id":"si23482","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_763","roles":{}},{"id":"si23379","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_750","title":"6.  Someone sends you a message on LinkedIn requesting your email to send you some attachments. You don’t know this person, but you see that you have a few mutual connections. Should you give them your email or other personal information? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23390","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_751","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23394","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_752","title":"Yes, you can trust people in your friends’ networks ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23390_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"175_407","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Yes, you can trust people in your friends’ networks\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si23401","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_753","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23405","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_754","title":"No, they are still a stranger ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23401_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"179_408","roles":{"answer":{"title":"No, they are still a stranger\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si23476","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_762","roles":{}},{"id":"si23504","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_119","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23522","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_120","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23544","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_121","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23562","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_122","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23574","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23586","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23598","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23610","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23622","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23634","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23646","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23658","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23446","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_759","title":"Correct - Answer:  B  Even if you share multiple connections with someone on social media, it doesn’t mean that they are safe to connect with or share information with.  Many of your friends have a large online social circle comprised of people they have never meet or known, this could leave them open to a social engineering or phishing attack. Also treat each unknown contact like a stranger.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23458","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_760","title":"Incorrect  - Answer:  B  Even if you share multiple connections with someone on social media, it doesn’t mean that they are safe to connect with or share information with.  Many of your friends have a large online social circle comprised of people they have never meet or known, this could leave them open to a social engineering or phishing attack. Also treat each unknown contact like a stranger.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23470","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_761","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide23671","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_194","si23379","si23394","si23405","si23504","si23522","si23544","si23562","si23574","si23586","si23598","si23610","si23622","si23634","si23646","si23658","si23470"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide23671"},"question":{"interactionId":"23359","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"6.  Someone sends you a message on LinkedIn requesting your email to send you some attachments. You don’t know this person, but you see that you have a few mutual connections. Should you give them your email or other personal information?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_195","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_195","roles":{}},{"id":"si23820","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_777","roles":{}},{"id":"si23717","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_764","title":"7.  If you have decided it’s time to join social media by creating an account and are excited about connecting online. What should you know before you start? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23728","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_765","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23732","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_766","title":"What information the social media company is collecting ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23728_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"175_411","roles":{"answer":{"title":"What information the social media company is collecting\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si23739","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_767","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23743","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_768","title":"How to protect your privacy ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23739_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"179_412","roles":{"answer":{"title":"How to protect your privacy\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si23750","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_769","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23754","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_770","title":"The dangers of using social media ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23750_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"399_413","roles":{"answer":{"title":"The dangers of using social media\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si24830","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24834","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"All of the above ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24830_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"All of the above\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si23814","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_776","roles":{}},{"id":"si23842","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_123","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23860","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_124","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23882","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_125","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23900","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_126","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23912","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23924","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23936","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23948","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23960","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23972","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23984","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23996","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23784","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_773","title":"Correct - Answer:  D  Before signing up for a social media account, it’s important to first understand what information the company collects and make an informed decision whether or not to join based upon that. While setting up an account, learn what privacy settings are provided and decide how and when to apply them. As well, search out educational material outlining the dangers of social media and how to best stay safe.   Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23796","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_774","title":"Incorrect  -  Answer:  D  Before signing up for a social media account, it’s important to first understand what information the company collects and make an informed decision whether or not to join based upon that. While setting up an account, learn what privacy settings are provided and decide how and when to apply them. As well, search out educational material outlining the dangers of social media and how to best stay safe.   Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23808","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_775","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide24009","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_195","si23717","si23732","si23743","si23754","si24834","si23842","si23860","si23882","si23900","si23912","si23924","si23936","si23948","si23960","si23972","si23984","si23996","si23808"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide24009"},"question":{"interactionId":"23697","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"7.  If you have decided it’s time to join social media by creating an account and are excited about connecting online. What should you know before you start?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["D"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_185","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_185","roles":{}},{"id":"Text_Caption_107","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_107","title":"Quiz Results ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6059","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si6083","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si6091","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si6055","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You Scored: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6079","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Total Questions: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6087","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Accuracy: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6103","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si6107","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"continue","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6121","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Review Quiz ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"review","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20489","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"continue","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20502","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"continue","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20517","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Review Quiz ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"review","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20530","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Review Quiz ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"review","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide6038","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide6038"}}},{"id":"si6231","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_186","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_186","roles":{}},{"id":"Button_4","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_4","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si19054","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si19068","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_9","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_9","title":" Stay Current With Information Security By Subscribing to the:   Weekly Security News Digest ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_298","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_298","title":"Thank you for taking the quiz.  To exit the quiz, close the browser window. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide6219","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si6231","Image_186","Button_4","si19054","si19068","SmartShape_9","Text_Caption_298"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":600},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide6219"}}},{"id":"Pool502","class":"pool","roles":{"pool":{"id":502,"name":"Pool1","questions":[]}}},{"id":"August2020Quiz","class":"project","title":"August2020Quiz","children":["Slide21706","Slide12483","Slide22259","Slide22582","Slide22905","Slide23333","Slide23671","Slide24009","Slide6038","Slide6219"],"roles":{"quiz":{"id":458,"branched":false,"submitAll":false,"review":true,"questions":["Slide12483q0","Slide22259q1","Slide22582q2","Slide22905q3","Slide23333q4","Slide23671q5","Slide24009q6"],"minScore":0,"maxScore":70,"passScore":56}}}],"contentSettings":{"global":{"branchAware":false},"toc":{"enabled":false},"playbar":{"enabled":true,"cc":false,"playPause":true,"back":true,"forward":true,"rewind":true,"close":true,"mute":true,"progressBar":true}},"contentReporting":{"CCCriteria":"quiz","CCData":{"quizData":"quiz_passed"},"SCCriteria":"quiz","SCData":{"quizData":"quiz_passed"},"exitNormalIfCompleted":false},"toc":[{"id":"Slide21706","title":"Slide 1"},{"id":"Slide12483","title":"Slide 2"},{"id":"Slide22259","title":"Slide 3"},{"id":"Slide22582","title":"Slide 4"},{"id":"Slide22905","title":"Slide 5"},{"id":"Slide23333","title":"Slide 6"},{"id":"Slide23671","title":"Slide 7"},{"id":"Slide24009","title":"Slide 8"},{"id":"Slide6038","title":"Slide 9"},{"id":"Slide6219","title":"Slide 10"}]}